spypig.com 2013-03-15

# SpyPig - Free Email Tracking System - Find out if your email has been read!

SpyPig is a free email tracking tool that lets you know when your recipient opens your email. 

SpyPig Website Privacy Policy   
Effective December 20, 2010 

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to information practices related to our website, [www.spypig.com](http://www.spypig.com/). Although this website contains links to other websites, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those, or any other sites. If you follow a link to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy. 

Personal Information Collected on this Website

No personally-identifiable information is collected on this website from consumers that browse the website for information or use the opt-out service. 

The only personally-identifiable information collected on this website is gathered on our "SpyPig Factory", "MySpyPig Factory", "SpyPig Stories", "Rate the Pig", "Tell-a-Friend", "Sign In" pages and others, where fields are provided so that you can provide your email address and/or name information. We collect this information so that we can email you the SpyPig notification, or respond to the comments that you send to us via that form, or allow you to sign in to our registered-user-only webpages. 

We also collect your IP address when you create a SpyPig tracking image on our "SpyPig Factory" or "MySpyPig Factory" page. This IP address is used to compare with your email recipient's IP address to check if you yourself open your own email. 

SpyPig is the sole owner of all information collected on this site. SpyPig will not rent, sell or share any personally-identifiable information about you with third parties for any reason except when required to assist in resolving an issue you raise with us or as required by law. 

We do not merge any of the personally-identifiable information collected via our contact form with other anonymous data collected on our website. 

Anonymous Information Collected on this Website

We record anonymous data such as traffic logs, number of visits or clicks on a given page, pages viewed or links to our site. We use IP addresses and cookies for gathering website statistics. We also store IP addresses on our server in the event that our site should become corrupted and it becomes necessary to discover the cause of this corruption. 

We aggregate this anonymous data as part of managing, maintaining and reporting on use of our website. We may share this anonymous data with third parties for the limited purpose of reporting on use of our website, or to comply with applicable law. We do not rent, sell or share any anonymous data collected on this website with third parties for marketing purposes. 

None of this anonymous data is linked to personally-identifiable information and we make no attempt to link IP addresses to the individuals who visit this Web site. 

Cookies

We use cookies on this website. Cookies are small chunks of data created by a web server, delivered through a web browser, and stored on your computer. They provide a means for websites that you visit to keep track of your online patterns and preferences, as well as identify you as a return visitor. Cookies make the personalization of your web experiences possible, so that you do not need to re-enter your information from scratch upon each visit to a given website. 

We serve a cookie from our website when users log in to registered-user-only pages, so that they can navigate those pages on the site. A randomly-generated anonymous identifier is assigned to that cookie to enable this process. 

We also serve a cookie to note the anonymous web traffic described in the previous section of this Privacy Policy. 

No personally-identifiable information is collected by or linked to any of the cookies delivered on our site. 

You have the ability to manage the use of cookies on your computer using controls in your web browser. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/. 

Third-Party Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, visit http://www.networkadvertising.org. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org. 

Changes to Our Privacy Policy

As our organization, membership and services evolve, this Privacy Policy may be revised to reflect those changes, where applicable. We therefore reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time, for any reason. Notice of such amendments will be posted as an updated Privacy Policy on this website, and an effective date will be indicated. Users are encouraged to check our site frequently to review the current Privacy Policy in effect. 

Questions?

Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
